# Firoz Ahmad

#### **Personal info**

Phone:

9987675496

Email:

firozahmad1989@gmail.com

Address:

4th Floor, Kamil Manzil, B-Block Brijpuri, New Delhi, 1110094 (IN)

### **Skills**

**Selling Skill** 















**Digital Marketing** 







**Business Development** 









**Team Management** 









## Professional Summary

Strategic-minded, goal-driven sales supervisor with over 7 years of verifiable successes in the areas of business development and team-leading. Exceptional ability to build and lead high-performing teams focused on developing profitable sales strategies and identifying market opportunities to achieve sales goals. An adaptable, customerfocused leader with a proven track record of bringing revenues, profits, and market shares to new heights.

# **Employment history**

## Area Sales Supervisor, Gulf Catering Company. Jeddah, KSA

Apr. 2016 - Sep. 2020

- A Team of 7 sales representatives, reporting to ASM.
- · Direct and coordinate activities involving sales of products, services, commodities, subjects of sale. manage daily forecast
- Ensure Customers getting promotions and schemes. Make sure the team achieved the sales targets and control the expiry
- Resolve customer complaints regarding sales and service.
- Track product distribution and resolve customer sales complaints

#### Marketing Executive, Pal Fashion Ltd. New Delhi

Dec. 2014 - Jan. 2016

- Reporting to the Area sales manager, handling Delhi.
- Visit new shops, existing customers, and make distributors.
- · Ensure the distributor gets proper schemes and product availability.
- · We have to achieve weekly and monthly sales targets.
- Develop prospect lists, pitch to them about products and services.

## Sales Officer, Procter & Gamble. New Delhi, Delhi

Jan. 2013 - Aug. 2014

- Reporting to sales supervisor, handling central New Delhi. A Visit is only existing 20-25 shops per day.
- Ensure aware of the current monthly offer and scheme. We have to achieve weekly and monthly sales targets.
- Explain products or services and prices and demonstrate the use of products. Resolve customer complaints regarding sales and service.

## Education

Annamalai University, Chidambaram, Tamil Nadu MBA, Marketing, Jun. 2012

Aligarh Muslim University, Aligarh, Uttar Pradesh

Bachelor of Arts, English Literature, May. 2010

Aligarh Muslim University, Aligarh, Uttar Pradesh

GED, History, English, Political Science, Jun. 2007